i2.com 2015-03-22

# JDA Privacy/Legal Statement | JDA Software

**THE CONDITIONS OF USE OF THIS SITE**  
This site is owned and operated by JDA Software Group, Inc. (“JDA”). By using JDA’s Web site, JDA.COM (“Web Site”), you signify your assent to these terms of use. If you do not agree to these terms of use, please do not use the site.

**TERMS FOR THE USE OF JDA’S WEB SITE**  
All materials on this Web Site are the property of JDA unless otherwise specified. No material from these pages may be copied, reproduced, republished, uploaded, posted, transmitted, or distributed in any way. For purposes of this Agreement, the use of any such material on any other Web site or networked computer environment is prohibited.

**DISCLAIMER**  
Postings are made at such times as determined by JDA in its discretion. Readers should not assume that the information contained on this Web Site has been updated or otherwise contains current information. JDA does not review past postings to determine whether they remain accurate, and information contained in such postings may have been superseded.

**LINKS TO OTHER MATERIALS**  
The linked sites are not under the control of JDA and JDA is not responsible for the content of any linked site or any link contained in a linked Web site. JDA reserves the right to terminate any link or linking program at any time. JDA does not endorse companies or products to which it links and reserves the right to note as such on its Web pages. If you decide to access any of the third party sites linked to this Web Site, you do this entirely at your own risk.

**APPLICABLE LAWS**  
This Web Site is controlled by JDA from its offices within the United States of America. JDA makes no representation that materials in the site are appropriate or available for use in other locations, and access to them from territories where their content is illegal is prohibited. Those who choose to access this Web Site from other locations do so on their own initiative and are responsible for compliance with applicable local laws. You may not use or export the Materials in violation of U.S. export laws and regulations.

**TRADEMARK NOTICE**  
Arthur, Decision Series, E3, Engage, Intactix, JDA, JDA Portfolio, Manugistics, MMS, Portfolio _Enabled_ , Timera, VistaCPG, and Win/DSS are registered trademarks with the United States Patent and Trademark Office, and Advertising and Promotion Management, _CategoryAdvisor_ , Intactix Knowledge Base, Intellect, JDALearn, JDA Intellect, JDA Marketplace, JDA Real Demand Chain Results, Performance Analysis by IDEAS, Planogram Converter, Planogram Generator, Portfolio, Portfolio BOS, Portfolio Infrastructure, Portfolio Knowledge Base, Portfolio Merchandise Management, Portfolio Merchandise Management System-I, Portfolio POS, Portfolio Registry, Portfolio Workforce Management, Real Demand Chain Results, and Trade Event Management are trademarks of JDA Software Group, Inc. Business Management Institute, BMI, Optimize on Demand, and Passport JDA are service marks of JDA Software Group, Inc. All other company and product names may be trademarks of their respective owners. The information contained herein is subject to change without notice.

**GENERAL**  
JDA may revise these terms at any time by updating this posting. You should visit this page from time to time to review the then-current terms because they are binding on you. Certain provisions of these terms may be superseded by expressly designated legal notices or terms located on particular pages at this site. Copyright © 1999-2014 JDA Software Group, Inc. All Rights Reserved. All other trademarks and copyrights are the property of their respective holders.

**PRIVACY POLICY**  
JDA is committed to respecting and protecting your privacy. To that end, we have prepared this Privacy Statement to disclose and describe our information gathering and dissemination practices for the Web Site.

**PERSONAL INFORMATION**  
In general, you may visit our Web Site without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information. Some portions of the Web Site may require you to give us personally identifiable information, which is information that enables us to identify you, such as your name, email or other address. Our primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide you with a smooth, efficient, and customized experience. This allows us to provide services and features that most likely meet your needs, and to customize our service to make your experience easier. However, privacy is very important to us. We recognize your right to confidentiality and are committed to protecting your privacy. We will not give, loan, or sell any personally identifiable information to any third party, unless legally required to do so. We may store and process personal information to better understand your needs. In addition we may use the information to contact you. If you use our Web Site to receive support services for a JDA product that you use, you may be required to supply personal information in order to receive these services via our Web Site, and we may use the information in order to perform services to you.

**NON-PERSONAL INFORMATION**  
In some cases, we may collect information about you that is not personally identifiable. Examples of this type of information include the type of Internet browser you are using, the type of computer operating system you are using, and the domain name of the Web site from which you liked to our Web Site.

**SECURITY POLICY**  
The importance of security for all personally identifiable information associated with our guests is of utmost concern to us. We use industry standard practices to safeguard the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information, such as firewalls and Secure Socket Layers. We treat data as an asset that must be protected against loss and unauthorized access. We also employ many different security techniques to protect such data from unauthorized access by users inside and outside JDA. However, “perfect security” does not exist on the Internet.

**IP ADDRESSES**  
We collect IP addresses for the purposes of system administration and to report aggregate information. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Internet. Web servers — the big computers that “serve” up Web pages — automatically identify your computer by its IP address. When guests request pages from our Web Site, our servers log the guests’ IP address. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable. This means that a user’s session will be logged, but the user remains anonymous to us. In addition, certain non-personally identifiable information is recorded by the standard operation of our Internet servers. This information allows us to keep our Web Site running efficiently. The information we record includes the browser (such as Netscape, Internet Explorer, etc.) and the operating system used (such as Macintosh, Windows 2000, etc.) by the visitor. Another use of this type of information includes the number of visitors to the various pages in our Web Site but only in a combined and non-personally-identifiable form. E-mail addresses and other personally identifiable information about visitors to our Web Site are known only when voluntarily submitted.

**COOKIES**  
We use a feature on your Internet browser called a “cookie.” Cookies are small files created on your computer’s hard drive. We use cookies to let it know that you are a prior customer. We also use cookies to retrieve certain information previously provided by you to our Web Site, so that you will not need to re-enter this information every time you visit our Web Site. We will not use cookies to store personal/business information.

Unless you specifically tell us, we will never know who you are, even though we may assign the browser on your computer a cookie. With most Internet browsers, you can erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block all cookies, or receive a warning before a cookies is stored. Please refer to your Internet browser’s instructions or help screen to learn more about these functions.

**EXTERNAL LINKS**  
As stated in the Legal Terms above, our Web Site contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

**ACCEPTANCE AND CHANGES**  
By using our Web Site, you signify your assent to our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Web Site. We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time based on your comments and our need to accurately reflect our data collection and disclosure practices. All changes will become effective immediately and you will not receive notice of these changes.

**CONTACTING THE WEB SITE**  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Web Site, or your dealings with our Web Site, please contact [webmaster@jda.com](mailto:webmaster@jda.com).

**ONLINE SOFTWARE LICENSE AND MAINTENANCE AGREEMENT**  
[Click here](http://jda.com/Software-License-and-Maintenance-Agreement) to view the standard online Software License And Maintenance Agreements.

**OTHER JDA LEGAL LINKS  **  
Click here to view standard Intactix Software License Agreements.
